{
    "subject": "resource/Lene_Lai",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1989-06-06",
    "human_readable": "Lene Lai was born on June 6, 1989.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8681129217147827,
            "question": "When was Lene Lai born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.855127215385437,
            "question": "Is Lene Lai's birthday in June?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8531731367111206,
            "question": "In what year was Lene Lai born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.719486653804779,
            "question": "What is Lene Lai's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6850095391273499,
            "question": "What month was Lene Lai born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.63062584400177,
            "question": "What month and day was Lene Lai born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.481587678194046,
            "question": "What is the day of the week on June 6, 1989?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39886006712913513,
            "question": "Is Lene Lai older than 30 years old?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39826077222824097,
            "question": "If today is October 26, 2023, how old is Lene Lai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2921631634235382,
            "question": "Calculate Lene Lai's age if the current date is June 15, 2024."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lene Lai was born on June 6, 1989.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2609_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If today is October 26, 2023, how old is Lene Lai?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2609_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Lene Lai older than 30 years old?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2609_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the day of the week on June 6, 1989?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2609_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2609_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2609_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2609_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2609_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2609_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2609_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2609_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2609_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2609_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2609_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently provide information that Lene Lai was born on June 6, 1989."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}